<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./BMX XXX (USA).iso</path>
		<name>BMX XXX</name>
		<desc>Slightly unusual for a tricks/stunt game, BMX XXX adds a twist to its genre by employing themes involving foul language, nudity and toilet humour.

The "Hardcore Tour" mode has you playing the levels, pulling off tricks and completing goals to unlock things such as new levels or stripper videos. The goals are of the odd variety, including things like collecting yellow snow for an icecream man, or gathering empty cans for a homeless guy. Also have to watch out for a health bar which accounts for your injuries and can make you start over levels if you run out of it.

Do well enough in the game and you unlock a topless mode, where the riders are all.. well.. 

There's also a 'create-a-ride' mode, and a two player split screen option, with different games of its own. The game plays on Acclaim's own Dave Mirra series' engine.</desc>
		<rating>0.5</rating>
		<releasedate>20031205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Z-Axis</developer>
		<publisher>AKA Acclaim</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Cycling</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GoldenEye - Rogue Agent (USA).chd</path>
		<name>GoldenEye : Rogue Agent</name>
		<desc>Why save the world when you can rule it? GoldenEye: Rogue Agent transports you to the dark side of the Bond universe as an aspiring 00 agent dismissed from MI6 for reckless brutality. You can customize and upgrade your villain persona and wreak havoc as you make your unrelenting rise through the ranks. You'll cross paths with such legendary allies and enemies as Oddjob, Scaramanga, Xenia Onatopp, and Pussy Galore on worldwide missions of vengeance and demolition. GoldenEye: Rogue Agent integrates single-player and multiplayer split-screen across all game modes.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20041126T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : Liberty City Stories</name>
		<desc>There are a million stories in Liberty City. This one changes everything. Once a trusted wise guy in the Leone crime family, Toni Cipriani was forced into hiding after killing a made man. Now he's back and it's time for things to be put right.

The streets of Liberty City are in turmoil. Warring mafiosi vie for control as the town begins to self-destruct under waves of political corruption, organized crime, drug trafficking and union strikes. No one can be trusted as Toni tries to clean up the mess of the city's chaotic underworld. Deranged hit men, morally depraved tycoons, cynical politicians and his own mother stand in his way as Toni tries to bring the city under Leone control.

Forced to fight for his life in an odyssey that will shake Liberty City to its foundations, Toni must use any means necessary to secure his place in the leadership of the Leone family in a town up for grabs.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA) (v3.00).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : San Andreas</name>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas takes place within the state San Andreas, which is based on sections of California and Nevada. It comprises three major fictional cities: Los Santos corresponds to real-life Los Angeles; San Fierro corresponds to real-life San Francisco; and Las Venturas and the surrounding desert correspond to real-life Las Vegas and the Nevada and Arizona desert.

The game features set co-op scenarios in a free roam mode as well as a cooperative "rampage" gameplay mode.</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20041029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA) (v4.00).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : Vice City</name>
		<desc>The player takes on the role of Tommy Vercetti, a man who was released from prison in 1986 after serving 15 years for killing eleven people. The leader of the organization for whom he used to work, Sonny Forelli, fears that Tommy's presence in Liberty City will heighten tensions and bring unwanted attention upon his organization's criminal activities. To prevent this, Sonny ostensibly "promotes" Tommy and sends him to Vice City to act as their buyer for a series of cocaine deals.[7] During Tommy's first meeting with the drug dealers, an ambush by an unknown party results in the death of Tommy's bodyguards, Harry and Lee, and the cocaine dealer. There is another survivor, the pilot of the dealer's helicopter, who flies off and escapes. Tommy narrowly escapes with his life, but he loses both the Forelli's money and the cocaine.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021108T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto : Vice City Stories</name>
		<desc>Vice City Stories is a prequel to Grand Theft Auto: Vice City (2 years earlier) and it is the sequel to Grand Theft Auto: Liberty City Stories. Set in 1984, players take on the role of Vic Vance, an army soldier who loves his country, family, and himself. One bad decision turns everything around and he is kicked onto the streets of a tough city. He has to build an empire to survive, or be left to die. Together with his brother Lance, a drug addict, the siblings try to take over Vice City.

Just like other GTA titles, gameplay consists of third-person shooting and driving sequences in an open environment. You will meet new enemies and gangs, and old foes. The missions require you to kill with a selection of weapons, steal vehicles such as a car, a boat, or a plane, rob to make it big, or just to have fun.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20070309T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Take 2 Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / RealTime 3D</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guilty Gear Isuka (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Guilty Gear Isuka</name>
		<desc>The next installment in the Guilty Gear sci-fi fighting series, in which bio weapons called Gears fight among each other for ultimate supremacy and survival, as they escape the so called Holy Knights who aim to hunt down and destroy them.

As with previous games in the series the game involves tournament-styled battles between characters using their special abilities and moves. However for GG Isuka the battles are 2-on-2 instead of 1-on-1, taking place in multi-plane arenas (similar to Fatal Fury) and requiring the players to switch orientation manually.

Added features include two new characters (only one playable), new backgrounds and game modes including the new "Boost" mode, which turns the game into a 2D side scrolling beat 'em up.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arc System Works</developer>
		<publisher>505 Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / Versus</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guitar Hero (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Guitar Hero</name>
		<desc>The game features a guitar-shaped controller (resembling a miniature Gibson SG) that the player uses to simulate playing rock music. The gameplay is similar to GuitarFreaks, in that the player presses buttons on the guitar controller in time with musical notes that scroll on the game screen. The game features covers of 30 popular rock songs spanning five decades of rock, from the 1960s up through 2005, in addition to bonus tracks. Guitar Hero became a surprise hit, earning critical acclaim and winning many awards from major video game publications, and was considered one of the most influential games of the first decade of the 21st century.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060407T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Harmonix Music Systems</developer>
		<publisher>RedOctane</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guitar Hero Encore - Rocks the 80s (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Guitar Hero : Rocks the 80s</name>
		<desc>Guitar Hero Encore: Rocks the 80s is an incremental title in the Guitar Hero series, using the features and gameplay from Guitar Hero II but with a completely new batch of songs. The game's theme is the eighties, reflected by the characters and their clothing, the venues and of course the songs themselves. It is the last title in the series developed by the original creators Harmonix Music Systems, Inc.
 As in the previous games, in the single-player mode the player works his way through a setlist unlocking increasingly difficult songs, divided over 4 main difficulties. By performing well, new songs and venues become available, but there are less unlockables compared to the previous titles. Notable bands in this edition include A Flock of Seagulls, The Police, Iron Maiden, Judas Priest, Asia, Dio and Anthrax. Unlike the previous games, there are no bonus tracks.
 The game is played through the guitar controller introduced for this series. The multi-player modes include Co-op, Face-off and Pro Face-off, identical to the previous game.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20070727T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Harmonix Music Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guitar Hero II (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Guitar Hero II</name>
		<desc>Guitar Hero II, the follow-up to the PS2-only game Guitar Hero, expands upon the gameplay and features of the original game. As a wannabe rockstar, you need to play songs by pressing combinations of five fret buttons on a guitar-shaped controller, while working the strum bar, along with an optional whammy bar for distortion. The sequel contains 64 songs, of which 40 have been licensed. One of the tracks was discovered through a contest at beaguitarhero.com, where unlicensed bands could send in a demo to be included in the game. Most of the tracks have been covered in-studio, but a few use original recordings.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Harmonix Music Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Guitar Hero III - Legends of Rock (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Guitar Hero III : Legends of Rock</name>
		<desc>Rock out to the third entry in in Red Octane's music series for guitar gods! Songs for Guitar Hero III include Barracuda by Heart, Sabotage by Beastie Boys, Rock And Roll All Nite by Kiss, and much more! In addition, players can experience an incredible number of added features and explosive content including a new multiplayer action-inspired battle mode, grueling boss battles, a bevy of exclusive unlockable content and authentic rock venues.

Also for the first time ever, Guitar Hero fans can thrash and burn with new wireless guitar controllers available for each platform. The exclusive Gibson guitars include innovative features such as removable faceplates that will allow fans to personalize their guitars and make it their own, and a new button color design that is integrated for an even greater authentic feel and rock experience.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20071123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Music</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jackass - The Game (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Jackass : The Game</name>
		<desc>The Jackass crew (minus Bam Margera) is in a jam, while getting ready to begin shooting for their much anticipated TV return, their one and only camera man is injured and it is up to you to get the show going. Take over as your favorite Jackass characters in a series of stunts to earn money to complete the episodes and get footage for the new season.

To earn money, complete certain tasks or injure yourself which will pay big money, once you earn enough money, your episode will be complete and you can move on to another. Completing episodes will unlock other characters, you get to start out with the core players (Johnny Knoxville, Steve-O, Ryan Dunn and Chris Pontius), while Wee-Man has his own mini-games, called Wee-Games which have ones like Roof Top Cart Stop, Poo Shower and Wee Tattoo.
</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20071123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sidhe</developer>
		<publisher>Red Mile Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Casual Game</genre>
		<players>2-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Medal of Honor - Frontline (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Medal of Honor : Frontline</name>
		<desc>Head back behind enemy lines with Lt. Jimmy Patterson in Medal of Honor Frontline. In this installment of the Medal of Honor series, Lt. Patterson is on a mission to infiltrate the German frontline and steal the HO-IX flying wing, an experimental Nazi weapon so powerful it could turn the tide of World War II. All 20 levels and six major missions in the game are based on real World War II events. You'll also find authentic weapons, including the Colt .45, Springfield sniper rifle, Panzerschreck rocket launcher, and Browning automatic rifle. The World War II experience just got more intense.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20020607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X - Command Mission (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Mega Man X : Command Mission</name>
		<desc>Mega Man X: Command Mission takes the blue bomber franchise in a whole new direction by adding RPG-style combat. Your mission is to infiltrate Giga City Island to stop the evil plans of the rioting Liberion Army. Choose from seven playable characters including Mega Man, Zero, and Axl, and team up to use three-member attacks. Upgrade your characters' abilities, attacks, and weapons to put an end to the brewing war. With cel-shaded characters, stylized environments, and a new "Cross Order System" that allows for finishing attacks, the Mega Man series looks to please both fans and gamers new to the franchise.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valuewave</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X7 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Mega Man X7</name>
		<desc>It is the 22nd century during an age when humans coexist with humanoid robots called "Reploids". As some Reploids participate in violent and destructive crime, a police organization called the "Maverick Hunters" was established to stamp out this activity. As always, Maverick crime is rising in newly constructed cities. As this new crime wave hits, X finds himself trying to answer moral questions that have plagued him since he joined the Maverick Hunters: "Are we doing the right thing to solve this matter?". Unable to assuage his conscience, he drops from the battle frontlines and assumes a more strategic support role at headquarters. With X's retirement, a massive power vacuum ensues and many independent groups develop, trying to fill the void left by the hunter. Prominent among these groups is the "Red Alert Syndicate", growing large enough to become a dominant force. They claim to hunt Mavericks, but apparently do more than that. One of their members, Axl, decides he's had enough of their "murdering" and tries to leave the group. Red, the group's leader, is angered by Axl deserting, and goes on a rampage to get Axl back.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20040305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valuewave</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X8 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Mega Man X8</name>
		<desc>Like its immediate predecessor, Megaman X8 presents its 2D-style platform-shooter action in a 3D game world. Mega Man X is joined in this adventure by two close associates, Zero and Axle, and each character has different strengths and abilities. Players can switch between two characters in the heat of battle, to solve a platform puzzle or fend of a particular enemy type, and the two characters not controlled by the player will try to help out in combat if the leading character becomes overwhelmed.
 Characters not controlled by the player recover more quickly when the hero onscreen is performing well. As in most games in the long-running Mega Man series, defeating a boss character earns the ability to use its special weapon. Other defeated enemies may leave behind metal bits, which can be collected and used to create custom power-ups. In addition to the side-scrolling platform levels, some boss fights and other events are played from alternate perspectives.
</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Valuewave</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Solid 3 - Snake Eater (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Solid 3 : Snake Eater</name>
		<desc>Hideo Kojima's critically acclaimed "tactical espionage action" series returns to PlayStation 2 in the anticipated follow-up to 2001's Sons of Liberty. Instead of slinking around futuristic installations, knocking on metal to distract guards, or crawling underneath a cardboard box, players are given a whole new Snake to wrangle. Drawing its inspiration from films like First Blood and Rambo: First Blood Part II, Snake Eater drops players in the middle of a thick jungle teeming with wildlife and, of course, terrorists.
 Heavily armed enemies dressed in camouflage gear will patrol the dense forests, waterfalls, and surrounding areas, so players will be able to climb trees, fire pistols while hanging down from branches, and crawl through hollowed out logs to stalk their prey. Along the way, Snake will have to find sustenance by catching fish or other wildlife, while being mindful of natural hazards such hornets nests, cliffs, and rapids. Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater was first revealed in a 12-minute preview displayed at 2003's E3 in Los Angeles, California.
</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20050304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Slug Anthology (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Metal Slug Anthology</name>
		<desc>The Metal Slug Anthology features seven previously released games in one package. The bundle includes Metal Slug, Metal Slug 2, Metal Slug X, Metal Slug 3, Metal Slug 4, Metal Slug 5, and Metal Slug 6. 
				 Two-player cooperative action is available, and the game also comes with a variety of unlockable content and a bonus gallery featuring a poster and classic character art.
</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20070706T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Terminal Reality</developer>
		<publisher>SNK</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Run and Gun</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat - Armageddon (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat : Armageddon</name>
		<desc>The fighting genre's poster (whipping?) boy for gruesome violence makes its final appearance on PlayStation 2 before moving in a new direction for Xbox 360 and PlayStation 3. Mortal Kombat: Armageddon is thus a hostile homage to its frenzied fans, a love letter of sorts that tears away the heart-tugging sentiment for the still-beating heart. Armageddon offers the most significant throng of Mortal Kombat fighters thus far, with a roster spanning 62 combatants -- every minor and major character that has appeared in the series to date. The entire cast is also immediately playable from the opening screen.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20061027T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Midway</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-8</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MTX Mototrax (USA).iso</path>
		<name>MTX Mototrax</name>
		<desc>MTX Mototrax is a motocross racing game that features motocross legends such as Travis Pastrana and Carey Hart. As players progress in the game's career mode, they will eventually be afforded the opportunity to challenge the mentioned pros in both Supercross and Motocross events as well as freestyle trick events where the focus is set on performing tricks. Winning these events will allow the player to earn cash and sponsorships that unlock additional gear and upgraded bikes. You can also play in exhibition mode to test your skills on any given track. The game features a total of 127 different tricks to perform.

The game also features a track editor that gives players the option of creating their own custom tracks. Multiplayer is also an available option. </desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>20040326T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Left Field</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving / Motorcycle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need for Speed - Hot Pursuit 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Hot Pursuit 2</name>
		<desc>Need for Speed is back and faster than ever in Need For Speed Hot Pursuit 2. Engage in the next generation thrill of arcade racing with the spiritual successor to Need For Speed III Hot Pursuit. The sequel houses a stable of exclusive and exotic cars from the world's most coveted licensors including Ferrari, Porsche, and Lamborghini. Become the "champion road racer" by conquering numerous racing events, all carrying rewards such as cars, tracks, and high performance upgrades. The game challenges the driver to dodge traffic, police, and natural elements in high speed and high style. And it's up to you to evade any cops on your path, since getting busted just might end your career.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Black Box</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need for Speed - Underground (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Underground</name>
		<desc>Need For Speed: Underground is the seventh game in the long running Need For Speed racing series. Underground revolves around illegal nighttime street racing with heavily modified import cars and has been greatly influenced by the movie "The Fast And The Furious" and its sequel.. Players get the chance to build their own racing machine almost from ground up, with hundreds or real licensed parts and lots of licensed cars, including the Mazda RX-7 and the Nissan Skyline GT-R. The game also features over 100 single player races and a hiphop/hardrock soundtrack including artists such as Mystikal, Rob Zombie and The Crystal Method.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Need for Speed - Underground 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Need for Speed : Underground 2</name>
		<desc>The next installment in the Need for Speed Underground series takes you to a free-roaming city comprised of five neighborhoods. As you explore the city, you'll encounter rival racers who will show you all the hot spots in underground racing. After each race, you can improve your car's performance with various upgrades, ranging from the gear ratio to the suspension. The game includes more than 30 tuner cars from a variety of manufacturers, such as Mitsubishi, Nissan, Toyota, and more. You can even challenge racers from around the world in the game's online mode.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20041119T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World Soccer Winning Eleven 2012 (Japan) (En,Ja).iso</path>
		<name>PES 2012 : Pro Evolution Soccer</name>
		<desc>Konami's "Winning" soccer series makes its 2012 return to the pitch, with play enhancements that give gamers more direct control of the ball and improvements to the artificial intelligence that controls teammates and opponents. "Off the Ball Control" allows gamers to move a cursor to quickly highlight and select any team player at any time. The game's "Pass Support" is adjustable through five settings, providing computer-assisted passes or allowing complete player control of a kick's direction and velocity.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20111028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Football (Soccer)</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fatal Frame (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Project Zero</name>
		<desc>Miku Hinasaki is young girl with a strange sixth sense. Her brother, Mafuyu, and his mentor, Junsei Takamine, went to investigate a mansion that once was inhabited by a powerful landowner who had absolute control over the area. Unfortunately, they never returned from their investigation. Miku enters the mansion, armed with only an antique camera given to her by her deceased mother, to try to find her brother.

While inside the mansion, Miku will encounter ghosts and other spiritual apparitions. In order to overcome these spirits and survive, she must use the magical camera to capture the ghosts on film, thereby trapping them forever. Ghosts range from invisible fragments hidden in scenery, to memories of the past that appear only for a moment before vanishing, to full body apparitions that will attempt to attack and kill Miku.

In order to defeat an aggressive ghost the Camera Obscura's shot must first be "charged" by keeping the ghost centered while it is visible. If Miku snaps a shot while the ghost is attacking or is vulnerable then she will drain even more energy from it, resulting in more spirit points being earned. Points can then be spent to improve her camera's attributes or give it special abilities, like slowing a ghost or pushing it away. The Camera Obscura can also reveal clues and dispel illusions, which Miku will need to utilize to solve puzzles within the mansion.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20021028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Wanadoo Edition</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fatal Frame III - The Tormented (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Project Zero 3 : The Tormented</name>
		<desc>The Fatal Frame series is back. Rei Kurosawa's fiancÃ©, Yuu Asou, dies in an ugly car accident when she is driving. She enters a haunted mansion as part of a reporting assignment. Here she is frightened by images of her dead fiancÃ©. The game incorporates the camera mode from the previous games, used to capture ghosts. You use the camera obscura not only as a weapon to capture ghosts but as a guide by taking pictures of the ghosts and creepy objects in the house in order to solve the mystery and get rid of the curse. You walk around with a strobe light looking for clues to the mystery.

Throughout the course of the game you can play as three women and switch between a dream world and real-life. All in all, it carries over the same Japanese horror theme as the first two.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20060224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Take 2 Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fatal Frame II - Crimson Butterfly (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Project Zero II : Crimson Butterfly</name>
		<desc>Twin sisters Mio and Mayu, while visiting a vacation spot from their childhood, become lost in a dark forest. The path disappears behind them as they enter the Lost Village, a place that vanished from the living world years ago. Ghosts of the townspeople walk the streets and search for the twins, intent on completing a dark ritual long left unfinished. Mayu begins to grow distant from Mio as well, and she begins to speak as if she were another person entirely. By chance Mio finds the Camera Obscura, and with its powers she searches for a way out get her sister and herself out of the village.

Fatal Frame II has mostly the same gameplay as the first game in the series, although with a few tweaks. The camera no longer has to charge up a shot, but different film types now have loading times that can leave leave Mio defenseless if she takes a picture at a bad time. Special abilities for the camera no longer require a disposable item, and are instead charged by taking good shots of attacking ghosts. The stats of the camera and special abilities are still upgraded/unlocked with spirit points, but an item must first be found and spent as well to upgrade each level of a stat.

The Xbox release of Fatal Frame II includes an additional difficulty level, an additional ending, several extra unlockable cosmetic accessories, six additional unlockable pairs of costumes for Mio and Mayu, an unlockable survival mode with an additional ghost type, and an optional first person control/view style.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Tecmo</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Dead Aim (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Resident Evil : Dead Aim</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil: Dead Aim, known as Gun Survivor 4: Biohazard: Heroes Never Die in Japan, is the fourth release in a series of light gun shooter video games by Capcom. It is also the first in the franchise to feature first-person shooting alongside the third-person movement seen in its predecessors in the Resident Evil series. It was developed by Capcom's Production Studio 3 and could be released for the PlayStation 2 as the company's then-effective exclusivity contract with Nintendo pertained only to numbered entries in the series.
 The Capcom series that helped establish the survival horror genre steps back into the faster-paced action of first-person shooting in Resident Evil: Dead Aim. In this Resident Evil: Survivor-style addition to the franchise, players join the dangerously brave Anti-Umbrella Pursuit Investigation Team operator Bruce McGivern as he guns down the baddies in an all-new storyline.
 Resident Evil: Dead Aim is designed to offer sharp graphics, steady action, and accessible gameplay. It supports Guncon 2 light gun controllers for a more authentic zombie-blasting experience. Remaining true to the spirit of the series, the game also features involved puzzle-solving, unsettling environments, and an abundance of creepy mutant monsters.
 </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20030709T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Cavia</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Lightgun Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Outbreak (USA) (v2.00).iso</path>
		<name>Resident Evil : Outbreak</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil - Outbreak takes a turn from previous outings in the survival horror series by featuring a multiplayer online component. The narrative is broken down into chapters, allowing up to four players to experience the world of Resident Evil together for the first time. Players initially choose from a lineup of eight characters, six males and two females, who each possess distinct skills or techniques. Some characters may be proficient in a specific style of weapon, while others may be able to open locked doors more efficiently.
The choice of characters becomes important since teamwork is often needed to advance through the zombie-filled office buildings, bars, subways, and dilapidated mansions in and around the cursed Raccoon City. The game also features a single-player mode for those brave enough to go it alone.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20040917T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Outbreak - File 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Resident Evil : Outbreak, File #2</name>
		<desc>Raccoon City has been infected by the Umbrella corporation's deadly T-Virus, a mutagenic toxin that turns its human victims into flesh eating zombies. The few survivors must try to escape the city before the government deploys its final solution to the problem of Raccoon City...

Once again you find yourself playing the eight characters of the original Resident Evil: Outbreak in more scenarios set in the ruins of what used to be Raccoon City. In single player mode you select a character to play and 2 other characters to accompany you.

The locales featured in this game include both familiar (The Raccoon Police Department) and exotic (A mutated jungle at mid-day) ones. The game is backwards compatible with your save file from Resident Evil: Outbreak, meaning that you can take your unlocked content to this new setting.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20050826T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Code - Veronica X (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Resident Evil Code : Veronica X</name>
		<desc>This title is a port of an important release in the Resident Evil series which was once available only for the Dreamcast console. The PlayStation 2 version of Resident Evil -- CODE: Veronica X is similar to the original Dreamcast release in nearly every relevant way though it contains additional cut-scenes.
 Resident Evil -- CODE: Veronica X picks up where the PlayStation's Resident Evil 2 left off, in Raccoon City. There, the Umbrella Corporation performed scientific experiments that went wrong. The result of their experiments was a virus that led to the creation of a huge number of zombies as well as a variety of other creatures bent on a path of death and destruction. As members of S.T.A.R.S. (Special Tactics and Rescue Squad), players did the best they could to stop the Umbrella Corp.'s madness, but ultimately Raccoon City and all of its inhabitants were wiped out.
</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill 2 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It) (v2.01).iso</path>
		<name>Silent Hill 2</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill 2 is not a direct sequel to the events and characters of the first Silent Hill game. Instead, it centers on James Sunderland, who enters the town after receiving a letter written by his deceased wife, saying she is waiting for him in their "special place" in Silent Hill. Joined by Maria who resembles her except for a more provocative outfit and personality, he searches for her and discovers the truth about her death. Additional material in re-releases and ports included Born from a Wish, a sub-scenario which focuses on Maria before she and James meet.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill 2 - Directors Cut (Europe) (EnFrDeEsIt).chd</path>
		<name>Silent Hill 2 : Director's Cut</name>
		<desc>In the sequel to Silent Hill, Silent Hill 2 follows James Sunderland, whose life is shattered when his young wife Mary suffers a tragic death. Three years later, a mysterious letter arrives from Mary, beckoning him to return to their sanctuary of memories, the dark realm of Silent Hill. You must guide James through all-new environments and creepy new areas closed off in the original game. Real-time weather effects, fog, morphing, and shadows set the stage for heart-stopping frights. Be brave as you journey to uncover the truth.

Director's Cut is an updated version of Silent Hill 2. It contains all of the content of the original version and adds several pieces of new content. The most significant is a new short scenario called Born from a Wish, where players take control of Maria from her first moments right up to where she first appears in the main game. Also included is a sixth ending to the main scenario and a minor feature that allows the player to turn off the graphical effect, which makes the game look like it was shot on cheap film stock.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill 3 (USA) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It,Ko).iso</path>
		<name>Silent Hill 3</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill 3 continues the series' trademark brand of psychological horror and terrifying gameplay. As a teenage girl named Heather, you'll explore and unravel the mysterious connection between the godforsaken town and her inner fears. Along the way, you'll encounter many strange characters you're not sure are trustworthy. Silent Hill 3 also features enhanced graphical detail, a more complex storyline, new items and weapons, and even more grotesque monsters than the previous games. Step into this world of nightmares and fight to survive.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20030805T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill 4 - The Room (USA) (En,Ja).iso</path>
		<name>Silent Hill 4 : The Room</name>
		<desc>Henry Townshend is a man living in a small apartment in South Ashfield, a neighboring town of the infamous Silent Hill. On one strange night, Henry has a terrible nightmare, with recurring events: his phone is dead, his windows are sealed, and his neighbors can't hear him. He looks at his door, only to see it is blocked by several thick metal chains. A note is pinned to the door: "Don't go out!" It is signed only by a man named Walter. Henry explores his apartment, trying to figure out what is happening, when he spots a giant hole in the wall of his bathroom. Henry goes through the hole, only to find a portal which leads him to alternate dimensions. Hopefully, Henry will find out the truth about his apartment, Room 302, and live.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20040907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill - Shattered Memories (USA) (En,Fr,Es).iso</path>
		<name>Silent Hill : Shattered Memories</name>
		<desc>Billed as a re-imagining of the original Silent Hill, Shattered Memories once again casts you as Harry Mason searching across the haunted town for his missing daughter Cheryl. New to the series are a depiction of Silent Hill's demonic alter-dimension as a world of ice, and the removal of weapons from the game - when the monsters come out, Harry must literally run for his life.

Between scenes, the game will cut to a psychiatrist's office, who asks you personal questions about yourself and your past experiences. The game will then alter itself based on your responses, changing characters and lines of dialog to something intended to be more personally uncomfortable.

As you search for Cheryl, you will come across objects and recordings that tell some of the history of Silent Hill.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20091213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill Origins (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).iso</path>
		<name>Silent Hill Origins</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill: Origins, known as Silent Hill: Zero in Japan, is the fifth installment in the Silent Hill video game series. It is a prequel to the original Silent Hill that was released in 1999. It was developed by Climax Studios and published by Konami. It debuted on the PlayStation Portable in November 2007, with a port to the PlayStation 2 released in March 2008.

Set seven years prior to the events of Silent Hill, Origins expands the backstory on which the series built itself.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20080304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Climax</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sly 2 - Band of Thieves (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Sly 2 : Band of Thieves</name>
		<desc>Thief and raccoon Sly Cooper returns in a new cel-shaded platforming adventure wherein he forms a band of thieves with Bentley the turtle and Murray the purple, hippo-like creature, which each have their own role within the game.

Sly is the fastest, most agile member of the band of thieves and still is the character you play with the most. But certain missions require the special abilities of Bentley, who is smart and can drop bombs, as well shoot enemies from a distance. Other missions require the muscles of Murray, who can lift nearly everything, including enemies.

The main goal of the game is the retrieval of a number of clockwork pieces from different locations around the world. Each theft has to be prepared with a number of sub-missions which have to be completed before the 'real thing' can begin.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20040914T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars - Battlefront II (USA) (v2.01).chd</path>
		<name>Star Wars : Battlefront II</name>
		<desc>Battlefront II features a more narrative-based campaign, retelling portions of the Star Wars story from the point of view of a veteran Imperial stormtrooper, reminiscing about his tour of duty in service of both the Galactic Republic and as part of the Galactic Empire. Gameplay additions over Battlefront include the use of Jedi, additional game modes, and objective-based space battles.

Two players can play splitscreen co-op throughout the story campaign or a strategic Galactic Conquest campaign.There is also a "comp stomp" configuration that supports 2 players offline, 2 players splitscreen online, or up to 16 players online.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20051101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Pandemic</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>2-24</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter EX3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Street Fighter EX3</name>
		<desc>The Street Fighter EX3 series returns with a third serving of tag-team, free-for-all brawls. Choose from 16 characters to play one-on-one, two-on-one, and even one-on-three battles. In original mode, take one character through a fighting quest and recruit your defeated opponents for tag or team play. With four gameplay modes and new enhancements such as the Critical Parade and Emotional Flow super moves, Street Fighter EX3 adds more fun to tag-team fighting.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20001014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Arika</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Simpsons, The - Hit &amp; Run (USA).iso</path>
		<name>The Simpsons : Hit &amp; Run</name>
		<desc>Explore Springfield as your favorite Simpsons characters as you unravel the plot that threatens the town's very existence. Play as Homer, Bart, Marge, Lisa, and Apu in over 56 driving and on-foot missions in seven challenging levels. Drive in 40 of Springfield's finest vehicles including Mr. Plow and the Canyonero. Unlock the multiplayer mode to play against three other players. The world of the Simpsons has many gags and surprises in store for you.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA) (Rev 1).iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<desc>This game saw the introduction of the revert, a trick that enabled vert combos to be tied together with a manual, by tapping a button when landing in a quarterpipe. This allowed for much longer combos than in the previous two games, where landing in a quarterpipe would finish a combo. The game also added hidden combos. These were variations on standard tricks that could be performed as grab, flip, lip, or grind tricks. For example, double-tapping the kickflip button would, naturally, make the character perform a double kickflip.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20011130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Activision</developer>
		<publisher>Neversoft</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (USA) (v2.01).iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4</name>
		<desc>Drop into the ultimate challenge. In the next chapter in the Tony Hawk series, pros challenge you to make your mark in huge free-roaming levels, taking on 190 progressively harder goals with no time limits to hold you back. Decide when you're ready to take on your Pro Challenge and move into the pro ranks, where it's a whole new game. Build your skills, perform all-new tricks, play up to eight players online, and show that you've got what it takes to go Pro.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20021122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal - Black (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal : Black</name>
		<desc>Twisted Metal: Black is a demolition derby that permits the usage of ballistic projectiles. Players choose a vehicle and an arena?or a series of arenas in the story mode?to engage in battle with opposing drivers. A variety of weapons and upgrades are obtainable by pick-ups scattered throughout the stage. The objective of the game is to be the last one standing.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20010618T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Incognito</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, TPV</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Black (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Black</name>
		<desc>Newton's third law is put to the test in Black, a first-person shooter from the development team behind the acclaimed Burnout franchise. Players are cast in the role of Jack Kelar, member of an elite tactical squad, whose team is assigned to Eastern Europe on a hunt for an American traitor. Rather than slinking through environments making quick, covert strikes, players in Black perform a full-on assault through nine levels of explosive action.
 A total of 13 cutting-edge weapons are available to eliminate the enemy threat, but the most distinguishing aspect of Black is its physics engine: fully destructible environments allow players the freedom to shoot inanimate targets as well as live ones. Instead of firing at a patrol of soldiers, for example, players can instead target nearby vehicles or barrels to trigger explosions, shoot out windows and balconies, and more. As Kelar blasts through the besieged cities, snow-covered wilderness, and other levels, shell casings, glass, dust, and debris will fly across the screen as plumes of smoke and raging fires dot the war-torn landscapes.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20060224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Criterion Games</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / FPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>12</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260413T110025</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Underground (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Underground</name>
		<desc>Get ready for a major new step for the Tony Hawk series. Tony Hawk's Underground tweaks the gameplay of previous installments to include a plot-twisting story, customizable tricks and decks, online play, and the ability to include your own mug shot on your custom player. Of course, you can also play as any one of pro skating's biggest stars including Tony Hawk, Bob Burnquist, and Elissa Steamer. Ride, walk, or drive through nine expansive levels then test your skills against other gamers online. Become a star of the Underground.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20031121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>275</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260413T131641</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Twinsanity (USA) (v2.00).iso</path>
		<name>Crash Twinsanity</name>
		<desc>Two purple birds called the Evil Twins form a new threat to Crash's homeworld. Crash has to team up with his arch rival Dr. Neo Cortex to put a stop to this new threat.

Crash Twinsanity is a classic-style Crash platform game, though this time Crash has to work together with Dr. Cortex from time to time. Crash can pick up and throw Dr. Cortex to places he can't reach himself, or use him as a hammer to slap enemies. The consistent conflict between both heroes causes many funny situations.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20041008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Traveller's Tales</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>136</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260413T132336</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
