<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Portuguese v110224)/Akumajou Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Japan) (Rev 2) (Track 2).bin</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Symphony of the Night</name>
		<desc>As a descendant of Dracula, you must end the vampire bloodline. Can you rid the world of this unspeakable terror? Uncover the mystery of Castlevania and challenge an adventure as legendary as its name. Over 140 different enemies, bosses, and ghastly creatures. Awesome magical spells - transform into a bat, a wolf, or etheral mist. Hidden weapons, secrets, and characters...the largest Castlevania ever!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<folder>
		<path>./Driver 2</path>
		<name>Driver 2 : Back on the Streets</name>
		<desc>You are an undercover driver, trying to survive amidst an international war between American and Brazilian gangs. The action takes you to Chicago, Las Vegas, Rio and Havana, all of which are depicted in detail, with curved roads added from the first game.

As before, you have full control over the car as it storms around the streets. A new feature is the ability to get out of the car, and carjack others. This is especially useful when you have fallen victim to the advanced damage modeling.

There is a full sequence of missions to complete, as well as some pre-set challenges and a Free Driving mode allowing you to explore at your leisure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./Driver 2/Driver 2 (USA) (Disc 1) (Rev 1).bin</path>
		<name>Driver 2 : Back on the Streets</name>
		<desc>You are an undercover driver, trying to survive amidst an international war between American and Brazilian gangs. The action takes you to Chicago, Las Vegas, Rio and Havana, all of which are depicted in detail, with curved roads added from the first game.

As before, you have full control over the car as it storms around the streets. A new feature is the ability to get out of the car, and carjack others. This is especially useful when you have fallen victim to the advanced damage modeling.

There is a full sequence of missions to complete, as well as some pre-set challenges and a Free Driving mode allowing you to explore at your leisure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Driver 2/Driver 2 (USA) (Disc 1) (Rev 1).cue</path>
		<name>Driver 2 : Back on the Streets</name>
		<desc>You are an undercover driver, trying to survive amidst an international war between American and Brazilian gangs. The action takes you to Chicago, Las Vegas, Rio and Havana, all of which are depicted in detail, with curved roads added from the first game.

As before, you have full control over the car as it storms around the streets. A new feature is the ability to get out of the car, and carjack others. This is especially useful when you have fallen victim to the advanced damage modeling.

There is a full sequence of missions to complete, as well as some pre-set challenges and a Free Driving mode allowing you to explore at your leisure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Driver 2/Driver 2 (USA) (Disc 2) (Rev 1).bin</path>
		<name>Driver 2 : Back on the Streets</name>
		<desc>You are an undercover driver, trying to survive amidst an international war between American and Brazilian gangs. The action takes you to Chicago, Las Vegas, Rio and Havana, all of which are depicted in detail, with curved roads added from the first game.

As before, you have full control over the car as it storms around the streets. A new feature is the ability to get out of the car, and carjack others. This is especially useful when you have fallen victim to the advanced damage modeling.

There is a full sequence of missions to complete, as well as some pre-set challenges and a Free Driving mode allowing you to explore at your leisure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Driver 2/Driver 2 (USA) (Disc 2) (Rev 1).cue</path>
		<name>Driver 2 : Back on the Streets</name>
		<desc>You are an undercover driver, trying to survive amidst an international war between American and Brazilian gangs. The action takes you to Chicago, Las Vegas, Rio and Havana, all of which are depicted in detail, with curved roads added from the first game.

As before, you have full control over the car as it storms around the streets. A new feature is the ability to get out of the car, and carjack others. This is especially useful when you have fallen victim to the advanced damage modeling.

There is a full sequence of missions to complete, as well as some pre-set challenges and a Free Driving mode allowing you to explore at your leisure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 2 : Cortex Strikes Back</name>
		<desc>After his defeat, Dr. Neo Cortex discovers the crystals that keep the world in balance. However, something is wrong: some of the crystals are missing. When the planets align, the chaotic flux created by the event will destroy the world. Cortex devises a plan to save the world by creating the Cortex Vortex.
 To help him save the world Cortex recruits his nemesis, Crash Bandicoot, to help him find the crystals. Take control of Crash as he travels to exotic locales like a space station, a waterfall, and Antarctica in 34 levels of running, jumping, and spinning action.
 Advance through the levels in any order you wish thanks to the level hub system. Will Crash be able to find all of the crystals? Can Dr. Cortex be trusted or is all of this an elaborate ruse? Play CRASH BANDICOOT 2: Cortex Strikes Back and find out.
 Features:
 * 34 levels with hidden areas and bonus levels
 * New moves and combo attacks
 * New interactive characters and enemies
 * Variety of challenging puzzles and mini-games</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19971206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot - Warped (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 3 : Warped</name>
		<desc>After defeating Dr. Neo Cortex, Crash and his sister, Coco, take a well-deserved vacation. However, their friend, Aku Aku, has a bad feeling, and as usual, he is right. Aku's evil twin, Uka Uka, was the person behind all of Dr. Cortex's schemes. Now Uka and Cortex have hatched a plot to gain control of the powerful crystals they desire. The have hired Dr. N. Tropy to create a time machine, which will allow Uka and Cortex to go back and take the crystals without interference. Take control of Crash and Coco as they travel through 30 levels across five time periods in an effort to stop Uka and Cortex. Use a motorcycle, plane, bazooka, and a baby T-rex to help Crash survive, or destroy the bad guys by using new moves like the super belly flop or the double jump. Will Crash and Coco be able to save the world? Play CRASH BANDICOOT: Warped and find out.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19981211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis</name>
		<desc>An abandoned research complex on a remote jungle island, a team of special forces operatives, a horde of vicious velociraptors, and one big, mean Tyrannosaurus rex constitute the setting and cast of Dino Crisis, the latest masterpiece from the makers of Resident Evil.
 Dr. Edward Kirk is supposed to be dead. Three years ago while working to establish a new type of energy technology code-named Third Energy, an experiment went awry and terminated the brilliant scientist's life -- or so it was thought. It was recently learned, however, that Dr. Kirk is very much alive and continuing his work at a Borginia Republic research facility on Ibis Island.
 In order to investigate the situation, an elite special forces team including agents Regina, Gail and Rick was sent. The three expected another routine mission, but what they got was an all-out fight for their lives against an enemy they surely had never been trained to face -- dinosaurs!
 Luckily, Regina isn't restricted to limited firepower, as she'll come across shotguns, dart guns, and other weapons throughout the island. To gain access to the keys, code disks, and ID cards necessary for continued exploration, Regina must solve a variety of puzzles.
 Dino Crisis has three possible endings with a great deal of secrets becoming available after each has been viewed. These include new weapons, new costumes, and a "Wipe Out" mode in which you must defeat a certain number of dinosaurs within a designated time period.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19991001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dino Crisis 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dino Crisis 2</name>
		<desc>Dino Crisis 2 is a third-person shooter video game for the Sony PlayStation, published by Capcom in North America, released on September 13, 2000 and publish by Virgin Interactive in Europe, release on November 4, 2000. It was developed by Capcom Production Studio 4. The game is the sequel to Dino Crisis and was followed by Dino Crisis 3 in 2003 and was ported to Microsoft Windows that same year.
 The story follows the events of the last game, where Regina is now on another mission involving a facility located close to the fictional Edward City, where a major anomaly has caused the whole island to be transported back in time to the era of the dinosaurs, along with all the human inhabitants. Regina is sent on a rescue mission with her new ally Dylan Morton, who has a strange connection to the events on the island. The player's control switches between Regina and Dylan at specific points in the game.
 </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20001124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / TPV</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dragon Ball GT - Final Bout (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Dragon Ball : Final Bout</name>
		<desc>After achieving cult hit status around the globe, Dragon Ball GT has finally arrived in the U.S. This polygon rendered fighting game features 10 of the best warriors from the animated television series going head-to-head in a no-holds-barred tournament. Each player has devastating finishing moves, including the infamous "Meteor Smash", which can be countered by an opponent, resulting in some of the most incredible power struggles you'll ever see! There are also 8 playable hidden characters and a practice mode that lets you build up the skills of each fighter. Now, you can find out what gamers around the world already know -- Dragon Ball GT is the ultimate fighting game!</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>19971106T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TOSE</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of Kain - Soul Reaver (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Legacy of Kain : Soul Reaver</name>
		<desc>1500 years after Blood Omen: Legacy of Kain, the vampire Kain's decision at the end of that game has finally defeated the human kingdoms and brought the world of Nosgoth under his control. Ruling from a castle built on the Pillars of Nosgoth, Kain has established an empire of six vampire clans, each ruled by a lieutenant, the sons of Kain. Raziel was one such lieutenant, but lost his position through the "insolence" of receiving a new evolutionary "dark gift", the growth of feathery wings, before his master had acquired it. Fearing that Raziel might one day surpass him, Kain tears off Raziel's wings in a fit of range and banishes him into the Abyss.  There, Raziel is lost in time, died and his body consumed. The Elder God recovers Raziel's soul and rebuilds the broken body, not as a living vampire, but as a strange new creature of the underworld. Swearing revenge on Kain, Raziel now phases seamlessly between Nosgoth and it's underworld, using his new powers to become a terrible reaver of souls...

Soul Reaver is a 3rd person action-adventure title that follows Raziel on his quest to purge the land of vampires and take revenge on Kain and his brothers, leaders of the six clans. The player controls the game from behind Raziel's shoulder, moving him in any direction, climbing, attacking, jumping and using specific abilities. Raziel's can grip onto the edge of ledges and his torn wings allow him to glide gently downwards. Raziel can shift through the "material" world into the "spectral" realm at will... but must find specific locations in order to shift back. The two realms mirror one another, with distortions which give access to new areas and platforms. Existing in the material world drains Raziel's life energy at a constant rate.  Throughout the game, energy is recovered by consuming the souls of defeated enemies. If Raziel is able to defeat one of his brothers, he will additionally gain a new ability ("dark gift") upon drinking it's soul. Examples include: the ability to swim, file telekinetic projectiles or the ability to phase through locked gates. Raziel can arm himself with a variety of weapons including spears, daggers, swords, axes, as well as attacking enemies barehanded. Eventually, Raziel will also come across Kain's personal sword (named the Soul Reaver), and will use it to create a powerful energy blade weapon.

The world is left open to Raziel, he can return to areas previously completed and explore the world of Nosgoth at will. Access to certain areas however sometimes  requires the use of gained specific abilities. Many of the puzzles the player will need to solve in this quest are "block puzzles", requiring the placement of certain large structures (usually square blocks), either to activate switches or to build access to out-of-reach areas.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990903T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mat Hoffmans Pro BMX (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX</name>
		<desc>Following in the tradition of the Tony Hawk Pro Skater series comes Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX. Choose from eight different professional BMX players and go from course to course accomplishing goals and trick points.
 Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX uses the same game engine seen in Tony Hawk Pro Skater, and has many of the gameplay elements have been retained. The dynamic camera always tracks your BMX rider from behind and switches to an aerial view when performing high jumps on half pipes. Collect magazine covers in each varied level (varying from city parks to warehouses) in order to unlock new levels. Players will have to execute high jumps and perform crazy tricks in the air and by railing metal bars and buildings in order to gain trick points. Enough trick points will allow you to unlock new levels.
 The soundtrack on Mat Hoffman's Pro BMX is also sure to appeal to almost any gamer, as a wide variety of song types have been covered, from rock to hip hop. Groups on the soundtrack include Outkast, Jurassic 5, Dead Prez, Deltron 3030 and Static-X.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20010516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shaba Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Cycling</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X5 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man X5</name>
		<desc>Years after the Reploid Wars, all seems peaceful in the world. But peace was not meant to last forever. When the "Eurasia" space colony is attacked by an unknown virus, the call goes out! X and Zero are called back into action to help destroy the colony, which is now on a collision course with Earth, and is expected to collide into the planet in only 16 hours! At the same time, guess who decides to show up once again...give you a hint: his name is a Greek letter.

With all new features like advanced Maverick AI, bigger, more challenging stages, new gameplay features like ducking and swinging on vines and ropes, this is set to be the most insane mission X and Zero have ever had to face!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20010803T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X6 (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man X6</name>
		<desc>Three weeks after the Eurasia space colony incident, the Earth's surface was severely damaged and humans were forced to flee underground to escape from the planet's severe pollution, and Zero is still missing, presumed to be dead. Reploids were sent in to terraform the land in an attempt to make the planet habitable for humans once more, however, a Reploid and former colleague of Alia named Gate discovered something unusual amidst the ruins of Earth — a piece of Zero's DNA. After examining Zero's DNA, Gate became mad with power and an outbreak of bizarre Mavericks occurred. Weeks passed, Isoc, a Reploid scientist and an associate of Gate, announced to the people that a new phenomenon known as "Nightmare" has quickly spread throughout the world, causing Reploids to hallucinate and eventually destroy themselves. Isoc suspects the cause of the outbreak is none other than Zero who been spreading the phenomenon as he goes, much to X's anger and confusion. Isoc rallies Reploids throughout the world to aid the Nightmare Investigators, led by the powerful High-Max, at key locations to track down the source of this new phenomenon as well as Zero. X, along with the Maverick Hunters, must confront the Nightmare Investigators as they try to solve the mystery behind the Nightmare Phenomenon and clear Zero's name.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20020208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat Trilogy (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat Trilogy</name>
		<desc>All the characters from the first three Mortal Kombat games return for the ultimate battle. You can play as Kano, Reptile, Mileena, Kung Lao, Shang Tsung, Sindel, Sketor, Stryker, Nightwolf, Sheeva, Kitana, Scorpion, Sonya, Smoke (Cyber Ninja), Rain, Jade, Baraka, Johnny Cage, Ermac, Noob Saibot, Sub-Zero (Unmasked), Sub-Zero (Classic), Jax, Rayden, Cyrax, Liu Kang, Smoke (Human), Kabal, Goro, Kintaro, Motaro, or Shao Kahn.

This game is one-on-one martial arts fighting. The player can choose from over thirty different characters, all with their own fighting style and their own special moves. Trilogy differs from the other games in that you can play combinations of people that otherwise isn't possible, such as old Liu Kang vs. new Liu Kang, etc.

Mortal Kombat Trilogy also allows you to challenge a friend to a fight through a Windows IPX network connection.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Avalanche Software</developer>
		<publisher>Midway</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 2D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 - Dual Shock Ver. (USA) (Disc 2).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2 (Claire Redfield Disc)</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil 2 takes place two months after the events of the first game and is set in Raccoon City, a Midwestern mountain community whose residents have been turned into zombies by the T-virus, a biological weapon developed by the pharmaceutical company Umbrella. In their escape from the city, the two protagonists Leon S. Kennedy and Claire Redfield encounter other survivors and are confronted by William Birkin, the mutated creator of the even more powerful G-virus.
 Previously confined to an old mansion, the Umbrella corporation's legacy of fatal mutations has spilled over into nearby Raccoon City. The once peaceful town is now overrun with zombies and all manner of genetic mutations. New police recruit Leon Kennedy and Claire Redfield; the sister of STARS agent Chris Redfield, find themselves in the middle of an experiment gone horribly wrong. </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980508T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 2 - Dual Shock Ver. (USA) (Disc 1).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 2 (Leon Kennedy Disc)</name>
		<desc>Resident Evil 2 takes place two months after the events of the first game and is set in Raccoon City, a Midwestern mountain community whose residents have been turned into zombies by the T-virus, a biological weapon developed by the pharmaceutical company Umbrella. In their escape from the city, the two protagonists Leon S. Kennedy and Claire Redfield encounter other survivors and are confronted by William Birkin, the mutated creator of the even more powerful G-virus.
 Previously confined to an old mansion, the Umbrella corporation's legacy of fatal mutations has spilled over into nearby Raccoon City. The once peaceful town is now overrun with zombies and all manner of genetic mutations. New police recruit Leon Kennedy and Claire Redfield; the sister of STARS agent Chris Redfield, find themselves in the middle of an experiment gone horribly wrong. </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19980508T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil 3 - Nemesis (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil 3 : Nemesis</name>
		<desc>Join Jill Valentine, the heroine and amazing survivor of the notorious disaster at the mansion, as her nightmare continues. After resigning from S.T.A.R.S. Jill now prepares to head out of Raccoon City...but it's not going to be easy. Caught in a town crawling with flesh eating zombies, more than ever she must rely on brute force and cunning to find a way to escape alive. This unique adventure intricately reveals more of Umbrella Corporation's nightmarish plot and picks up just hours before the events from Resident Evil 2.

More zombies, more terror, and even more evil.
More challenging enemies that come back to life at any time.
Face off against the most terrifying mutations stalking the streets of Raccoon City.
More detailed character actions: Try the dodge move to avoid an enemy's attack.
Interact with the environment like never before: Use background objects defensively.
A unique new drama which reveals more details of Umbrella Corporation's devious activities from the Resident Evil series.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20000317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<playtime>18</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260411T224326</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Resident Evil - Directors Cut - Dual Shock Ver. (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Resident Evil : Director's Cut</name>
		<desc> After receiving a distress call from the Bravo Team, an elite group from S.T.A.R.S (Special Tactics And Rescue Squad) flew into the desolate Raccoon City. Apparently, the team had uncovered something concerning the Umbrella corporation -- a biotech research company. But then, without warning, the Bravo Team vanished into thin air.
 Upon landing in the small city, the members of S.T.A.R.S began to investigate. They heard some strange noises coming from the surrounding woods and realized the sounds were getting closer. Scared, they took off running and kept on until they came to a large, ominous mansion. Seeking safety they entered, locking the door behind them. Their adventure had just begun.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19960801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Silent Hill (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Silent Hill</name>
		<desc>Silent Hill is a 1999 survival horror video game for the PlayStation. The first in a series about a mysterious town of the same name, Silent Hill generated a direct sequel, three indirect sequels, a prequel and a film adaptation. The game was included in Sony's Greatest Hits and Platinum Range of budget titles as a result of strong sales. A reinterpretation of the game was developed for the Wii, PlayStation 2 and PlayStation Portable.
The plot focuses on Harry Mason as he searches for his daughter, Cheryl, who has disappeared following a car accident which left Harry unconscious. He finds Silent Hill to be largely abandoned, shrouded in a thick fog, snowing out of season, filled with monsters and being over taken by a hellish otherworld. As Harry scours the town, he begins learning about the history of Silent Hill and stumbles upon a cult ritual undertaken to bring a god to Earth.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19990801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Silent</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure / Survival Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man 2 - Enter - Electro (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 2 - Enter: Electro</name>
		<desc>Spider-Man 2 - Enter: Electro is the second PlayStation game to feature Spider-Man, and also serves as the sequel to the 2000 video game Spider-Man. This game follows Spider-man as he attempts to stop his old enemy Electro from obtaining a source of power called the Bio-Nexus Device. Game bosses included Hammerhead, Lizard, Sandman, Shocker and the exclusive charged-up Hyper-Electro.

This sequel to Activision's 2000 multi-platform Spider-Man release features the title villain in a diabolical scheme to construct a device that will amplify his strange electricity-based powers and make him virtually unstoppable. Players take the role of their friendly neighborhood Spider-Man to foil Electro's plan before it's too late. Movement and camera angles are similar to those of the first Spider-Man game, though Spidey has a few new web-slinging abilities in this title and is challenged by some sophisticated puzzle-solving and complex action sequences. Once again, Marvel Comics' legendary Stan Lee provides narration for this adventure.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tekken 3</name>
		<desc>An ancient evil force has reawakened, attacking in secret and feeding on the souls of mighty warriors. To lure it out of hiding will take the greatest fighting contest the world has ever seen... Tekken 3. Some are fighting for revenge, some for honor, ultimately, all are fighting for their lives and the fate of all mankind.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>19980912T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting / 2.5D</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawks Pro Skater 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2</name>
		<desc>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2 features the series' trademark open-ended gameplay, in which the player (playing as a professional skateboarder) completes a number of tasks which result in cash rewards. With money gained, the player can then purchase skill improvements and better skateboards. THPS2 was also the first game in the series to introduce the manual, a skateboarding trick where the performer balances on two wheels. This enables players to string together trick combos. The game also introduced the Noseslide, Tailslide, Bluntslide, Nosebluntside, Feeble, and Overcrook grinds. It was also the first of the Pro Skater games to feature Create-a-Skater and Park Editor features, now staples in the series.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20000929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawks Pro Skater 4 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4</name>
		<desc>Drop into the ultimate challenge. In the next chapter in the Tony Hawk series, pros challenge you to make your mark in huge free-roaming levels, taking on 190 progressively harder goals with no time limits to hold you back. Decide when you're ready to take on your Pro Challenge and move into the pro ranks, where it's a whole new game. Build your skills, perform all-new tricks, play up to eight players online, and show that you've got what it takes to go Pro.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>20021115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Vision</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal : World Tour</name>
		<desc>Twisted Metal features destructive car combat, playable either as a complete tournament or a single match The action takes place in 8 different locations around the world, on differing surfaces, many featuring destructible buildings and landmarks.

Combat takes place between a wide array of vehicles ranging from a man strapped between two wheels to an ice cream truck. They have their own strengths and weaknesses,  using an eclectic arrangement of weaponry include bombs and missiles, and resulting in its own end sequence, complete with an ironic line in humour.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SingleTrac</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, TPV</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Twisted Metal III (USA) (Rev 1).chd</path>
		<name>Twisted Metal III</name>
		<desc>In an apocalyptic future, the mysterious and powerful Calypso offers one wish to the winner of the Twisted Metal competition.

The Twisted Metal competition consists of vehicular combat between souped-up and weaponed-out machines such as a motorcycle, police car, ice cream truck, and even a man with wheels for arms.  The battles take place in locations from around the world, including London and Tokyo.</desc>
		<rating>0.7</rating>
		<releasedate>19981111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>989</developer>
		<publisher>989</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter / Vehicle, TPV</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Destruction Derby 2 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Destruction Derby 2</name>
		<desc>Strap in, hold on, hit the gas, and you're off on a quest for destructive points in Destruction Derby 2, the smashing sequel to the original demolition derby game from Reflections Interactive and Psygnosis. This edition offers seven larger tracks with lots of jumps and flips, as well as the dreaded crisscross sections where huge damage often ensues. Choose one of three cars and take your pent-up rage into one of four bowl arenas or one of four circuit courses. Let the mayhem begin!
 The new Pit Stop feature allows the player to make repairs to a damaged vehicle and head back out into the fray. Realistic physics deforms cars (and their nice paint job) as you collide with 19 other racers. The game's physics engine allows wheels, car hoods and other debris fly to everywhere. Localized damage adds an element of strategy too, as headfirst ramming destroys engines and can quickly take the driver out of the game. Players will have to develop some strong techniques or they'll be stalled on the sidelines by the middle of the game.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19970215T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reflections Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Psygnosis</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Driving</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>178</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260412T095627</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X4 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Mega Man X4</name>
		<desc>It is the year 21XX, following years after the Doppler rebellion and the revelation of the Maverick Virus, a new global Reploid military force, apty-named Repliforce, was founded to combat the ongoing Maverick attacks and uprisings. However, humans quickly began to fear and distrust Repliforce's military power and their methods of fighting Mavericks proved to be very destructive with little disregard for human life. One day, the floating city Sky Lagoon was under attack by Mavericks and Repliforce arrived on the scene after the city has crash landed on the ground, where one of their leaders, Colonel, was being ordered by the Maverick Hunters X and Zero to lower his weapons for questioning as suspects for the incident. Out of pride and contempt towards human government, Colonel refused to comply, and following the accusations behind the Sky Lagoon incident, the Repliforce General decided stage a coup d'état, seeking to create a new utopia just for Reploids. Repliforce were then labeled as Mavericks by the government, thus the Maverick Hunters must fight against their former allies and stop their coup.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19981204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Platform / Shooter Scrolling</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>93</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260412T095817</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawks Pro Skater 3 (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<desc>You may not be able to live like the legend, but now you can skate like him. Skate as the legendary Tony Hawk or choose from a dream team of 12 top pro skaters, including old favorites like Lasek, Thomas, Muska, and Steamer, as well as new talent like Gilfberg, Caballero, Koston, and Mullen. Or enjoy full customization abilities with the enhanced Create-a-Skater (now including female skaters) and the Skatepark Editor. Travel from L.A. to Tokyo, Suburbia to Skater's Island performing challenges and meeting goals. New moves include the Revert, which allows you to link vert tricks, and flatland tricks such as Caspers, the Primo, and Handstand Manual. If you're good, you can even unlock hidden pro footage.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20011123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Shaba Games</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports / Skateboard</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>82</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260413T105959</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot</name>
		<desc>Crash Bandicoot, a heroic, agile and mutated marsupial who must save his girlfriend Tawna. The main antagonist is Doctor Neo Cortex, a mad scientist who was often ridiculed by the scientific community for his outlandish (but nearly workable) theories and is now motivated to prove his tormentors wrong by creating a mutated army of beasts to conquer the world. Cortex's henchman is Doctor Nitrus Brio, the insecure creator of the Evolvo-Ray. Crash's love interest is Tawna, a female bandicoot about to undergo experimentation by the Doctors. Helping Crash in his journey is an ancient witch doctor spirit named Aku Aku, who has scattered masks of himself throughout the islands to grant Crash special powers. The boss characters of the game include Papu Papu, the obese and short-tempered chief of the native village; Ripper Roo, a demented kangaroo with razor-sharp toenails; Koala Kong, a muscular but unintelligent koala; and Pinstripe Potoroo, the tommy gun-wielding bodyguard of Doctor Cortex.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>19961102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>17</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260415T134435</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Portuguese v110224)/Akumajou Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Japan) (Rev 2) (Track 1).bin</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Symphony of the Night</name>
		<desc>As a descendant of Dracula, you must end the vampire bloodline. Can you rid the world of this unspeakable terror? Uncover the mystery of Castlevania and challenge an adventure as legendary as its name. Over 140 different enemies, bosses, and ghastly creatures. Awesome magical spells - transform into a bat, a wolf, or etheral mist. Hidden weapons, secrets, and characters...the largest Castlevania ever!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>2</playcount>
		<playtime>9</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260418T170408</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<folder>
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Portuguese v110224)</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Symphony of the Night</name>
		<desc>As a descendant of Dracula, you must end the vampire bloodline. Can you rid the world of this unspeakable terror? Uncover the mystery of Castlevania and challenge an adventure as legendary as its name. Over 140 different enemies, bosses, and ghastly creatures. Awesome magical spells - transform into a bat, a wolf, or etheral mist. Hidden weapons, secrets, and characters...the largest Castlevania ever!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lastplayed>20260418T170418</lastplayed>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./Akumajou Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Portuguese v110224)/Akumajou Dracula X - Gekka no Yasoukyoku (Japan) (Rev 2).cue</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Symphony of the Night</name>
		<desc>As a descendant of Dracula, you must end the vampire bloodline. Can you rid the world of this unspeakable terror? Uncover the mystery of Castlevania and challenge an adventure as legendary as its name. Over 140 different enemies, bosses, and ghastly creatures. Awesome magical spells - transform into a bat, a wolf, or etheral mist. Hidden weapons, secrets, and characters...the largest Castlevania ever!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>4</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260418T170418</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Symphony of the Night (USA).chd</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Symphony of the Night</name>
		<desc>As a descendant of Dracula, you must end the vampire bloodline. Can you rid the world of this unspeakable terror? Uncover the mystery of Castlevania and challenge an adventure as legendary as its name. Over 140 different enemies, bosses, and ghastly creatures. Awesome magical spells - transform into a bat, a wolf, or etheral mist. Hidden weapons, secrets, and characters...the largest Castlevania ever!</desc>
		<rating>1</rating>
		<releasedate>19971101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>KCET</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>87</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260418T170551</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
