<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Extra Games/Pokken Tournament DX [0100B3F000BE2000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Pokken Tournament DX [0100B3F000BE2000][v0]</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>12</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260413T214249</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<folder>
		<path>./Extra Games</path>
		<name>Extra Games</name>
		<lastplayed>20260413T214549</lastplayed>
	</folder>
	<game>
		<path>./Extra Games/Metroid Prime 4 Beyond Switch XCI Base Game.xci</path>
		<name>Metroid Prime 4 Beyond Switch XCI Base Game</name>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>65</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260413T214549</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legacy of Kain Defiance Remastered [0100760026272000].nsp</path>
		<name>Legacy of Kain Defiance Remastered</name>
		<desc>Return to the dark world of Nosgoth as you take control of both the vampire Kain and his betrayed lieutenant, Raziel, two powerful entities bound by the conflict between free will and fate.

Armed with legendary blades and supernatural abilities, battle through towering gothic spaces filled with enemies, puzzles, and long-buried secrets – where no victory comes without a cost.

Experience a timeless dark fantasy reborn for a new generation.

Legacy of Kain: Defiance Remastered has been updated with new HD graphics, refined controls, and a modernized game camera with the ability to toggle between the HD and original presentation any time. This new edition also boasts a photo mode, alternate character skins, a comprehensive lore reader, and unreleased content and 'lost levels' from the original game.

Dual Protagonist
Play as both Kain and Raziel, each with distinct abilities, combat styles, and perspectives that shape how the story unfolds.

Dark Fantasy and Rewarding Puzzles
Explore ruined cities, ancient temples, and towering strongholds filled with environmental puzzles, challenging enemies, and horrible secrets.

Faithfully Remastered for Modern Play
Updated HD visuals, refined controls, and a modernized camera, with the option to switch between modern and classic presentation at any time.

Character Skins
Earn alternate skins for both Kain and Raziel inspired by the Legacy of Kain canon.</desc>
		<releasedate>20260331T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics</developer>
		<publisher>Crystal Dynamics, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scott Pilgrim EX [0100D59022590000].nsp</path>
		<name>Scott Pilgrim EX</name>
		<desc>Join Scott Pilgrim and Ramona Flowers in a brand-new brawling adventure across space, time, and the streets of Toronto!
Toronto, 20XX. The city has been taken over by 3 rival gangs - the VEGANS, the ROBOTS, and the DEMONS. But who’s behind this madness? When Scott Pilgrim’s bandmates are abducted by shadowy forces, a brand-new adventure begins!

Scott Pilgrim EX is an action-adventure game where players can fight as Scott Pilgrim, Ramona Flowers and more as they battle through the fractured time and space of Toronto. The combat gameplay is driven by instinct and improvisation - a hectic ballet of fists and flair that rewards strategy, spontaneity, and a good bit of brawling chaos. String together stylish combos, experiment with wacky weapons and unleash over-the-top special attacks. Characters can be upgraded with special badges that enhance their stats and grant special bonuses. Players will explore a whole city of interconnected levels to meet old and new faces, complete quests, and discover hidden areas. Multiplayer co-op, local or online, lets up to four players join in on the action, making it a fun, dynamic experience.

- 7 Playable Characters
Step into the shoes of seven fan-favorite fighters, each with their own distinct combat style.

- A Brand-New Adventure
Venture out on epic quests and battle new enemies and bosses across interconnected levels in a new story by series creator Bryan Lee O’Malley that will appeal to longtime fans and newcomers alike.

- Madcap Melee Mayhem
Master creative combos, wield wacky weapons, use your surroundings to your advantage and conquer the chaos!

- Power Up!
Spend your hard-earned coins to customize your fighter! Equip special items and upgrade your stats to create a unique build for every playthrough!

- New Anamanaguchi Music
Known for their explosive blend of 8-bit energy and hyper-melodic rock, the band returns to their roots with all new music crafted for this Toronto-hopping adventure.

- 4-Player Co-Op Mayhem
Join forces with up to three friends, locally or online, with easy drop-in/drop-out co-op. Battle solo or hit the streets together.</desc>
		<releasedate>20260303T000000</releasedate>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bendy and the Ink Machine[0100D4C00C6C0000][GB][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Bendy And The Ink Machine</name>
		<desc>"Bendy and the Ink Machine™" is a first person puzzle action horror game that begins in the far days past of animation and ends in a very dark future.</desc>
		<releasedate>20181120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>TheMeatly Games</developer>
		<publisher>Rooster Teeth Games</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bendy Lone Wolf [010071B022A36000].nsp</path>
		<name>Bendy: Lone Wolf</name>
		<desc>Step into the inky nightmare of Bendy: Lone Wolf®, a thrilling survival adventure set in the twisted, rubberhose world of Joey Drew Studios. As Boris, the lone wolf, you’ll brave endlessly shifting corridors filled with monstrous cartoon creeps, deadly traps, and the relentless pursuit of the Ink Demon. Every day brings new challenges in this heart-pounding quest for survival and truth.</desc>
		<releasedate>20251024T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>Joey Drew Studios</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania Dominus Collection (World) (En,Ja,Fr,De,Es,It) (eShop).nsp</path>
		<name>Castlevania : Dominus Collection</name>
		<desc>In addition to the three action adventure games from the Castlevania series, Haunted Castle Revisited, an redesigned version of the very first Castlevania arcade game, makes its debut! And you can also play it in its original format!
Experience the world of Castlevania like never before, with never-before-seen art and handy new features such as rewind, quick saves and much more! Titles 
Castlevania: Dawn of Sorrow
The adventures of Soma continue! Discover a completely new way to create countless weapons by combining souls, in stunning 2D graphics.
One year after the events of Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow, a boy named Soma Cruz is once again put at the center of a plot to resurrect Dracula led by a mysterious cult.. Will he finally be able to face his own destiny and put an end to all this?
Castlevania: Portrait of Ruin
Not one but two heroes join their forces to fight the evil this time! Switch between Jonathan and Charlotte with a single button press and make the best use of their unique abilities.
Dracula's Castle has suddenly resurfaced, but something doesn't add up.
Jonathan Morris and Charlotte Aulin make their way in to investigate, they soon discover that the mind behind all this is not who they thought...
Castlevania Order of Ecclesia
The enigmatic Shanoa is the only human capable of using the glyphs, symbols full of magic.
Gather glyphs by exploring the Castle and its surroundings and absorb the power of the mighty foes you fight!
The three most powerful glyphs, thought to be able to even defeat Dracula himself, have been stolen. Can Shanoa bring them back to the Order, and finally destroy the Dark Lord?
Haunted Castle
Haunted Castle Revisited, a redesigned version of the very first Castlevania arcade game, makes its debut! And you can also play it in its original format!</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20240827T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>M2</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Role Playing Game</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Contra Operation Galuga [0100CF401A98E000].nsp</path>
		<name>Contra: Operation Galuga</name>
		<desc>A new entry in the legendary Contra series is here! Contra: Operation Galuga is a thorough reimagining of the classic run-'n'-gun action game from the '80s, featuring modern graphics and sound, new stages, new enemies and bosses, new play mechanics, an updated weapons system, and explosive co-op combat for up to two players in Story Mode or four players in Arcade Mode!
When the Red Falcon terrorist group takes over the Galuga Islands off the coast of New Zealand, elite Contra commandos Bill Rizer and Lance Bean springs into action, initiating an all-out war in which the fate of mankind hangs in the balance!
Run, jump, and shoot your way through eight levels using a devastating arsenal - including the spread shot, laser, and homing missiles - now with stackable upgrades and awesome Overload abilities! The intense action is customizable with three difficulty settings plus a variety of additional challenge options. The true Contra legacy begins now! Key </desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20240312T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Cult of the Lamb [01002E7016C46000][v0][Base].nsp</path>
		<name>Cult of the Lamb</name>
		<desc>Start your own cult in a land of false prophets, venturing out into diverse and mysterious regions to build a loyal community of woodland worshippers and spread your Word to become the one true cult. BUILD YOUR FLOCK 
Collect and use resources to build new structures, perform dark rituals to appease the gods, and give sermons to reinforce the faith of your flock. DESTROY THE NON-BELIEVERS 
Explore a sprawling, randomly generated world, fight off hordes of enemies and defeat rival cult leaders in order to absorb their power and assert your cult's dominance. SPREAD YOUR WORD 
Train your flock and embark on a quest to explore and discover the secrets of five mysterious regions. Cleanse the non-believers, spread enlightenment and perform mystical rituals on the journey to become the mighty lamb god.</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20230414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Massive Monster</developer>
		<publisher>Devolver Digital</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country Tropical Freeze [0100C1F0051B6000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country : Tropical Freeze</name>
		<desc>Arctic invaders have turned Donkey Kong Island into their personal frozen fortress, and it's up to you to save the day. Play as Donkey Kong in Original Mode and team up with Diddy Kong, Dixie Kong, and Cranky Kong—each with unique abilities—to overcome platforming challenges and frosty foes.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20180504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Retro</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokken Tournament DX [0100B3F000BE2000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Pokkén Tournament DX</name>
		<desc>Pokémon comes to Nintendo Switch Introducing the first Pokémon title for the Nintendo Switch console. Take direct control of one of 21 prized Pokémon fighters to defeat other Pokémon in arena fights. Call upon Support Pokémon to assist in the fight, then unleash your Pokémon's unique Burst Attack to climb atop the ranks. With all new modes and new ways to battle with friends, this is your chance to become champion of the Ferrum Region!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20170922T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow of the Ninja Reborn [010072601DB8C000].nsp</path>
		<name>Shadow Of The Ninja Reborn</name>
		<desc>It’s 2029. A vicious dystopian future. And it’s up to two warriors of the night to save the nation!
After 33 years in the shadows, prepare to see this legendary action adventure in a new light! Looking and playing better than ever before, Shadow of the Ninja - Reborn is Tengo Project’s remake of a cult classic, that the fans have been waiting for.
In this thrilling action-adventure, you will use your striking katana along with a wide variety of weaponry that has greatly expanded from the NES original, as well as the acrobatic finesse of a ninja to face the onslaught of powerful enemies. Although, the challenge does not end here! 6 complex, expansive, and masterfully designed stages test your skills through devious traps and challenging platform puzzles.
Critically acclaimed as one of the best 2-player co-ops of its time, Shadow of the Ninja—Reborn lets you play together locally as the legendary ninjas Hayate and Kaede.
In addition to the contributions of Tengo Project, this remake also features Iku Mizutani, the star composer who helped create the iconic Natsume sound and renowned tracks for various NES games. Fans of Mr. Mizutani and retro gamers across the world will find delight in his renowned guitar riffs and fast-paced retro melodies!
Our fearless heroes, Hayate and Kaede have undergone a massive visual upgrade over their original 8-bit models. And the improvements don’t stop there: From the deadly foes to the no-less deadly stages, every part of this title has been faithfully recreated in stunning high-quality sprites.
So, cloak yourself in shadows and slash your way through a treacherous concrete jungle of the future in this dark action gem Shadow of the Ninja – Reborn!</desc>
		<releasedate>20240829T000000</releasedate>
		<publisher>ININ Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shantae Half-Genie Hero[0100AE0003424000][US][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Shantae: Half-Genie Hero Ultimate Edition</name>
		<desc>Shantae: Half-Genie Hero Ultimate Edition is a vibrant, action-packed platformer starring the half-genie hero Shantae. When a mysterious crime wave hits Sequin Land, Shantae must use her signature hair-whip attacks, belly dance transformations, and magical abilities to save the day. Explore a vast interconnected world, battle quirky enemies and bosses, and uncover secrets hidden throughout the levels. This ultimate edition includes all the previously released DLC, offering new playable characters like Risky Boots and Shantae's friends, along with extra modes and costumes. With its stunning hand-drawn animation, catchy soundtrack, and charming cast of characters, Shantae: Half-Genie Hero Ultimate Edition is a delightful experience for fans of platforming and action games.</desc>
		<releasedate>20180427T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Wayforward</developer>
		<publisher>Wayforward</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 3D All-Stars[010049900F546000][US][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Super Mario 3D All-Stars</name>
		<desc>Play three classic games at home or on the go -- all in one package on the Nintendo Switch system! Jump into paintings in Super Mario 64, clean up paint-like goop in Super Mario Sunshine, and fly from planet to planet in Super Mario Galaxy.

Make Mario move using the Nintendo Switch system's Joy-Con controllers. You can also pass a Joy-Con controller to a friend to play the Super Mario Galaxy game in Co-Star Mode! Mario's movements are as smooth as ever with HD resolution for each game, while still retaining the look and feel of the originals.

Listen to a total of 175 iconic tunes from all three games! Whether you want to get up and dance or take a minute to relax -- this collection has music to fit your mood!</desc>
		<rating>0.8</rating>
		<releasedate>20200918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Maker 2 [01009B90006DC800][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Super Mario Maker 2</name>
		<desc>Make it Your Way, Play it Your Way.

Mario fans of the world, unite! Now you can play, create, and share the side-scrolling Super Mario courses of your dreams in the Super Mario Maker 2 game, available exclusively on the Nintendo Switch system! Dive into the single-player Story Mode and play built-in courses to rebuild Princess Peach's castle. Make your own courses, alone or together. And with a Nintendo Switch Online membership, share your courses, access a near-endless supply made by others, enjoy online multiplayer, and more!

A new side-scrolling Mario adventure that unleashes the creative potential of Super Mario Maker 2 awaits in Story Mode, which contains over 100 built-in courses. And in Course Maker, a wide range of parts, tools, and more are available so you can construct your own courses. Want coin-shooting cannons? Bowser riding on a giant Goomba? Cat Mario sliding down slopes to take out an army of baddies? Go for it! You call the shots.</desc>
		<rating>0.9</rating>
		<releasedate>20190628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./The Binding of Isaac꞉ Afterbirth+ [US][010021C000B6A000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>The Binding of Isaac: Afterbirth+</name>
		<desc>Isaac has discovered a labyrinth beneath his own house, filled with monsters, power-ups and unimaginable treasure. Can he survive the physical challenges and psychological trials of a world he never made?

The Binding of Isaac: Afterbirth+ is a dungeon-crawling shoot-'em-up that's literally a different game each and every time you play it! The randomly generated maps are built with over 11,000 unique room configurations, each populated with a nearly endless variety of enemies, items, challenges and secrets!</desc>
		<releasedate>20170907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nicalis</developer>
		<publisher>Nicalis</publisher>
		<genre>Action / Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./THE NINJA WARRIORS ONCE AGAIN [010036200CF6A000][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Ninja Warriors: Once Again, The (Ninja Saviors: Return of the Warriors, The)</name>
		<desc>The good old days of beat-‘em-up action are back – the Ninjas have returned!
In TAITO’s latest arcade action masterpiece you’ll slip into the role of one of five android ninjas and brawl your way through waves of enemy hordes in a dystopian future.
Over a total of eight levels, you’ll take on the tyrant Banglar and his henchmen either alone or - for the first time in the history of the series - with a friend. So settle into a night on the couch with your friends, and reminisce about the golden era of 90s co-op game evenings you know and love.
The original developers, TENGO PROJECT, have improved the audio-visuals in every respect, making an already outstanding game even better!
Along with two completely new characters, the fully revised side-scrolling arcade brawler also offers fans a plethora of individual moves, new 16-bit pixel art graphics and animations, the revamped sound of TAITO’s legendary house band ZUNTATA as well as an online ranking system so that you can compare your skills to fighters from all over the world.</desc>
		<releasedate>20190830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Natsume</developer>
		<publisher>ININ Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unravel Two[0100E5D00CC0C000][US][v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Unravel Two</name>
		<desc>Chase the spark of adventureWinner - D.I.C.E. Awards Family Game of the Year.When you cut ties to the past, new bonds form. In Unravel Two, create a Yarny of your very own. Then build relationships with other Yarnys in local co-op or as a single player, fostering friendship and support as you journey together.Begin your adventure in a cold and imposing land, then watch your surroundings blossom with new life as you chase the spark of adventure. Dive into an immersive story filled with energy, exuberance, inspiration – even monsters. Approach every challenge with positivity and fearlessness to awaken the world around you, and discover an unbreakable bond between friends.Nintendo Switch™ Mode Support- Tabletop- TV- Handheld (single player only)</desc>
		<releasedate>20190322T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Coldwood Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles  Mutants Unleashed [010013001BD62000][v0][US].nsp</path>
		<name>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles : Mutants Unleashed</name>
		<desc>Mutants and humans have been kickin’ it together in New York City. But then, Leonardo, Raphael, Michelangelo, and Donatello discovered several shipments of mutagenic ooze were scattered, contaminating areas of the City. It didn’t seem so bad until they realised new mutants, a.k.a. 'Mewbies', spawned from this mess. Not all these Mewbies are evil, but some have lost their way, and the citizens don't feel safe anymore.
Join the legendary Turtle brothers straight from the sewer and slide into this new adventure of shell-shocking proportions. With the help of April’s insightful reports from the streets and Splinter’s sage guidance, gear up to fight crime and unravel an epic saga of justice and chaos!
Embark on the adventure in single or co-op mode to change the minds of the citizens, get those pizzas delivered on time, and try not to eat them on the way.
CHOOSE YOUR TURTLE AND MASTER YOUR NINJA SKILLS – Play as the legendary brothers, Raphael, Michelangelo, Leonardo, and Donatello.
HANGOUT IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD AND SEWERS – Help the citizens, find the mewbies, deliver pizzas, and build your graffiti collection.
RISE TO THE CHALLENGE TOGETHER - Team up with a friend in two-player couch co-op.
INSPIRED BY THE MOVIE – Continue the mayhem in the search for mewbies.</desc>
		<rating>0.6</rating>
		<releasedate>20241018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AHEARTFULOFGAMES</developer>
		<publisher>Outright Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1-2</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<playtime>5</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260418T220927</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Creaks [0100B0E010CF8000] [v0].nsp</path>
		<name>Creaks</name>
		<desc>Meet Your New Neighbors
The ground starts shaking, light bulbs are breaking - and something rather unusual is happening right behind the walls of your very room. Equipped with nothing but wit and courage, you slowly descend into a world inhabited by avian folk and seemingly deadly furniture monsters.

From the creators of indie classics Machinarium and Samorost comes Creaks, a new puzzle adventure game that delights the senses with its hand-painted visuals, precise animation, eerie sounds, and an eclectic original score from Hidden Orchestra. Proceed at your own pace at figuring out the solutions to dozens of carefully designed puzzles, explore the mansion for hidden paintings and uncover the great secret.</desc>
		<releasedate>20200722T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Amanita Design</developer>
		<publisher>Super Rare Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok [010085500D5F6000][v2.0.0][US][Base].nsp</path>
		<name>Turok</name>
		<desc>Turok is back and no dinosaur is safe! When it was first released in 1997, Turok introduced gamers to a world teeming with cunning enemies, traps, puzzles and deadly weapons all within a vast 3D environment ready to explore. Now the classic game has been restored and enhanced with a new visual engine and exciting new features to sink your teeth into!

The Lost Land...

A world where time has no meaning - and evil knows no bounds. Torn from a world long gone, the time traveling warrior Turok has found himself thrust into a savage land torn by conflict. An evil overlord known as 'The Campaigner' seeks to shred the fabric of time and rule the universe using an ancient artifact known as 'The Chronoscepter'. The Chronoscepter was shattered thousands of years ago in an effort to keep it from falling into evil hands. The Campaigner has constructed a massive focusing array which he plans to use to magnify and pervert the power of the Chronoscepter in order to shatter the barriers between the ages and rule the universe. Turok has vowed to find the eight pieces of the Chronoscepter spread throughout the Lost Land and put an end to The Campaigner's evil plot...</desc>
		<releasedate>20190318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Night Dive Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Night Dive Studios, LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<playcount>4</playcount>
		<playtime>41</playtime>
		<lastplayed>20260415T225401</lastplayed>
	</game>
</gameList>
